const science = [
  {
    question: "Meteorology is the study of?",
    answers: ["atmosphere", "winds and clouds", "air and sounds", "seasons"],
    correct: "atmosphere",
    questionId: "31"
  },
  {
    question: "White light passing through a prism splits into?",
    answers: ["8", "5", "6", "7"],
    correct: "7",
    questionId: "15"
  },
  {
    question: "Primary colours of Light?",
    answers: ["Red, Green, Blue", "Red, Orange, Blue", "White, Black, Blue", "Red, Yellow, Blue"],
    correct: "Red, Green, Blue",
    questionId: "32"
  },
  {
    question: "Primary colours of pigments?",
    answers: ["Red, Green, Blue", "Red, Orange, Blue", "White, Black, Blue", "Red, Yellow, Blue"],
    correct: "Red, Yellow, Blue",
    questionId: "33"
  },
  {
    question: "Diamond is a form of?",
    answers: ["Carbon", "Hydrogen", "Oxygen", "Silicon"],
    correct: "Carbon",
    questionId: "34"
  },
  {
    question: "1 nanometer= ?",
    answers: ["10-6m", "10-6m", "10-9m", "10-12"],
    correct: "10-9m",
    questionId: "16"
  },
  { question: "SI unit of Heat?",
    answers: ["Coulomb", "Ohm", "Volt", "Joule"],
    correct: "Joule",
    questionId: "35"
  },
  {
    question: "Good sources of Vitamin-A?",
    answers: ["green leafy vegetables", "fresh vegetables and fruits", "seeds", "sea foods"],
    correct: "green leafy vegetables",
    questionId: "36"
  },
  {
    question: "Good sources of Vitamin-B complex?",
    answers: ["green leafy vegetables", "fresh vegetables and fruits", "seeds", "sea foods"],
    correct: "seeds",
    questionId: "37"
  },
  {
    question: "Good sources of Vitamin-C?",
    answers: ["green leafy vegetables", "fresh vegetables and fruits", "seeds", "sea foods"],
    correct: "fresh vegetables and fruits",
    questionId: "38"
  },
  {
    question: "Good sources of iodine?",
    answers: ["green leafy vegetables", "fresh vegetables and fruits", "seeds", "sea foods"],
    correct: "sea foods",
    questionId: "39"
  },
  {
    question: 'What gas is called "laughing gas"?',
    answers: ["Sodium Oxide", "Carbon Dioxide", "Sulfur Dioxide", "Nitrous Oxide"],
    correct: "Nitrous Oxide",
    questionId: "40"
  },
  {
    question: "What is GPS?",
    answers: ["Global Position Structure", "Global Positioning System", "Global PolySiliconium Store", "Global Poles Systember"],
    correct: "Global Positioning System",
    questionId: "19"
  },
  {
    question: "What is oxidation?",
    answers: ["Loss of Electrons", "Gain of Protons", "Loss of Protons", "Gain of Electrons"],
    correct: "Loss of Electrons",
    questionId: "20"
  },
  {
    question: "Where is urine produced?",
    answers: ["Liver", "Kidneys", "Lungs", "Large intestine"],
    correct: "Kidneys",
    questionId: "21"
  },
  {
    question: "Blood is cleaned by?",
    answers: ["Liver", "Kidneys", "Lungs", "Large intestine"],
    correct: "Kidneys",
    questionId: "22"
  },
  
  {
    question: "The energy value of food is measured in ____?",
    answers: ["Calories", "Joule", "Tesla", "Proteins"],
    correct: "Calories",
    questionId: "41"
  },
  {
    question: "Wind energy is a _____ energy?",
    answers: ["Potential", "Mechanical", "Kinetic", "Transverse"],
    correct: "Kinetic",
    questionId: "42"
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is considered the founder of meteorology?',
    answers: ["Einstein", "Aristotle", "Plato", "Newton"],
    correct: "Aristotle",
    questionId: "43"
  },
  {
    question: "The fourth state of matter is?",
    answers: ["Water", "Salts", "Plasma", "Vapours"],
    correct: "Plasma",
    questionId: "44"
  },
  {
    question: "Copper can be converted into gold by?",
    answers: ["heating", "Artificial radioactivity", "Chemical reaction", "Electroplating"],
    correct: "Artificial radioactivity",
    questionId: "45"
  },
  {
    question: "Bronze medal is made up of?",
    answers: ["copper, silver", "copper, zinc", "copper,nickel", "copper, tin"],
    correct: "copper, tin",
    questionId: "46"
  },
  {
    question: " Humming birds are?",
    answers: ["Ectotherms", "Endotherms", "Exotherms", "Heterotherms"],
    correct: "Endotherms",
    questionId: "47"
  },
  {
    question: "Isotope of Uranium in Nuclear Bomb?",
    answers: ["92 U 234", "92 U 238", "92 U 235", "92 U 233"],
    correct: "92 U 235",
    questionId: "48"
  },
  {
    question: "Percentage of water in milk?",
    answers: [
      "80",
      "60",
      "70",
      "90"
    ],
    correct: "80",
    questionId: "3"
  },
  {
    question: "SI unit of charge?",
    answers: ["Coulomb", "Ohm", "Volt", "Ampere"],
    correct: "Coulomb",
    questionId: "4"
  },
  {
    question: "Very High Frequency have ____ wavelengths?",
    answers: ["longest", "longer", "shortest", "shorter"],
    correct: "shorter",
    questionId: "5"
  },
  {
    question: 'Deficiency of Vitamin-A results in?',
    answers: ["scurvy", "rickets", "Night blindness", "hair fall"],
    correct: "Night blindness",
    questionId: "6"
  },
  {
    question: " The Lifespan of Red Blood Cells is ____ days?",
    answers: ["100", "120", "25", "68"],
    correct: "120",
    questionId: "7"
  },
  {
    question: "SI unit of pressure?",
    answers: ["Coulomb", "Ohm", "Pascal", "Ampere"],
    correct: "Pascal",
    questionId: "14"
  },
  {
    question: "Percentage of alcohol in spirit?",
    answers: [
      "80",
      "60",
      "70",
      "95"
    ],
    correct: "95",
    questionId: "49"
  },
  {
    question: "Least abundant element in the Earth's crust?",
    answers: ["Carbon Dioxide", "Radium", "Oxygen", "Silicon"],
    correct: "Radium",
    questionId: "50"
  },
  {
    question: 'A light year is a unit of?',
    answers: ["Energy", "Time", "Length", "Mass"],
    correct: "Length",
    questionId: "24"
  },
  {
    question: "Density of water?",
    answers: ["1g/cm3", "4g/cm3", "2g/cm3", "3g/cm3"],
    correct: "1g/cm3",
    questionId: "8"
  },
  {
    question: "Who discovered radioactivity?",
    answers: ["Bacquerel", "Kelvin", "Rutherford", "Thomson"],
    correct: "Bacquerel",
    questionId: "9"
  },
  {
    question: "The sun is a ____?",
    answers: ["Star", "Planet", "Meteor", "Asteroid"],
    correct: "Star",
    questionId: "10"
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the outermost in the solar system?",
    answers: ["Neptune", "Jupiter", "Venus", "Mars"],
    correct: "Neptune",
    questionId: "1"
  },
  {
    question: "Deficiency of Vitamin-D results in?",
    answers: ["osteomalacia", "scurvy", "rickets", "night blindness"],
    correct: "rickets",
    questionId: "2"
  },
  {
    question: "Which is easily visible from the Earth?",
    answers: ["Neptune", "Jupiter", "Venus", "Mars"],
    correct: "Venus",
    questionId: "23"
  },
  {
    question: "Which planet is closest to the Earth?",
    answers: ["Mercury", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Venus"],
    correct: "Mercury",
    questionId: "17"
  },
  {
    question: "Average adult blood volume in litres?",
    answers: ["5", "3", "6", "4"],
    correct: "5",
    questionId: "11"
  },
  {
    question: "Most abundant element in the universe?",
    answers: ["Carbon Dioxide", "Hydrogen", "Oxygen", "Silicon"],
    correct: "Hydrogen",
    questionId: "12"
  },
  {
    question: "Most abundant element in the Earth's crust?",
    answers: ["Carbon Dioxide", "Hydrogen", "Oxygen", "Silicon"],
    correct: "Oxygen",
    questionId: "13"
  },  
  {
    question: "Which planet moves around the Sun with the highest speed?",
    answers: ["Mercury", "Saturn", "Jupiter", "Mars"],
    correct: "Mercury",
    questionId: "18"
  },
  {
    question: "Which planet is closest to the Earth?",
    answers: ["Mercury", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Venus"],
    correct: "Mercury",
    questionId: "17"
  },
  {
    question: "Which planet is referred to as Earth's bodyguard?",
    answers: ["Mercury", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Venus"],
    correct: "Jupiter",
    questionId: "25"
  },
  
  {
    question: "Planets visible from earth without telescope?",
    answers: ["5", "3", "4", "6"],
    correct: "5",
    questionId: "26"
  },
  {
    question: "SI unit of electric current?",
    answers: ["Coulomb", "Ohm", "Volt", "Ampere"],
    correct: "Ampere",
    questionId: "27"
  },
  {
    question: "Most abundant element in the Earth's crust?",
    answers: ["Carbon Dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Oxygen", "Silicon"],
    correct: "Nitrogen",
    questionId: "28"
  },
  {
    question: "What is Dry Ice?",
    answers: ["Solid Carbon Dioxide", "Solid Nitrogen", "Solid Oxygen", "Solid Hydrogen"],
    correct: "Solid Carbon Dioxide",
    questionId: "29"
  },
  {
    question: "Where is digestion completed?",
    answers: ["Liver", "Kidneys", "Lungs", "Large intestine"],
    correct: "Large intestine",
    questionId: "30"
  },
];

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(science.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
